landoflinks.com 2006-06-18

# Land of Links: Privacy Policy

|    |   [Home](http://www.landoflinks.com/index.html) > Privacy Policy 

* * *

LandofLinks.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: **Information Automatically Logged** We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to produce statistical visitor data reports. 

**E-mails Automatically Sent**

When a web page is submitted to LandofLinks.com, contact information from the site is collected including email addresses. This information is used only to notify the point of contact that their site was successfully added to our database. They are also notified when they modify their site listing in our database. We do not make their e-mail addresses available to any organizations. 

**Advertisers** We use a variety of outside ad companys to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we do not use cookies in any part of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.  **External Links** This site contains links to other sites. LandofLinks.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  **Public Forums** LandofLinks.com makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  **Contacting LandofLinks.com** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of LandofLinks.com, or your dealings with LandofLinks.com, you can contact: 

---|---|---  
  
Copyright © 2000-2006 Landoflinks.com. All rights reserved.
